BUI DANG NHA



Contact

Address:

28/132 Dai Linh Trung Van Ha Noi

Phone:

0919893549

Email:

dangnhabui@gmail.com

Github:

Project 1: Car infotainment system https://github.com/nhonbonchel/githubProject

Project 2: Media Player https://github.com/nhonbonchel/mediaPlayer

Education

Automotive Certificate FUNiX, 2021 - 2022

Automotive engineering technology University of Transport Technology, 2016 - 2021

Summary

I have finished 5 years of university studies and have some experience working in the garage during my internship. After graduation, I work in Manh Hung auto parts company as warehouse staff.

I always wanna try learning programming and in December 2021, I finally made up my mind and registered for an Automotive Application Development with C++ course in FUNIX. I found it fits me perfectly, I almost finished the course and am eager to get a job.

Skill Highlights

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, C++, Python
- Bootstrap, Qt
- Pycharm, Jupyter Notebook
- Logical thinking
- Team management, communication and estimation

•

Experience

Technician - 05/2021 to 08/2021 **Kim Long garage** HaNoi City

maintenance and repair auto parts
support client to know which part need to repair

Warehouse Staff - 09/2021 to 03/2022 Manh Hung auto parts Company HaNoi City

- Support transporting goods to the warehouse
 - Inventory items in stock
 - Manage the quantity of spare parts in warehouse
 - Take out the product that need to be sold